<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Rebecca J. Stevick</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Rebecca J. Stevick</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>`&amp;copy;` Rebecca Stevick `{year}`</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Estuarine acidification and oyster health</title>
      <link>/project/estuarineacidification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/estuarineacidification/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out our web app that describes the environmental conditions and oyster characteristics in Narragansett Bay: &lt;a href=&#34;google.com&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://rjstevick.shinyapps.io/nbay_shinyapp/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://rjstevick.shinyapps.io/nbay_shinyapp/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This work was supported by the URI Coastal Institute, The Nature Conservancy of RI - TNC Global Marine Team, NSF Graduate Research Fellowship 1244657 to RJS, and the Blount Family Foundation. This material is based upon work conducted at a Rhode Island NSF EPSCoR research facility, the Genomics and Sequencing Center, supported in part by the National Science Foundation EPSCoR Cooperative Agreement #OIA-1655221.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutrient enrichment and oyster microbiomes</title>
      <link>/project/denitrification/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/denitrification/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This work was supported by RI SeaGrant, the URI Coastal Institute, The Nature Conservancy of RI - TNC Global Marine Team, NSF Graduate Research Fellowship 1244657 to RJS, and the Blount Family Foundation. This material is based upon work conducted at a Rhode Island NSF EPSCoR research facility, the Genomics and Sequencing Center, supported in part by the National Science Foundation EPSCoR Cooperative Agreement #OIA-1655221.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oyster-associated microbial transcriptomes</title>
      <link>/project/transcriptmining/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/transcriptmining/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This work was supported by NSF Graduate Research Fellowship 1244657 to RJS. This material is based upon work conducted at a Rhode Island NSF EPSCoR research facility, the Genomics and Sequencing Center, supported in part by the National Science Foundation EPSCoR Cooperative Agreements 0554548, EPS-1004057, and OIA-1655221.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Probiotics in oyster larviculture</title>
      <link>/project/probiotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/probiotics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Related publications:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/fmicb-2019/&#34;&gt;Stevick, R.J., Sohn, S., Nelson, D.R., Rowley, D.C., Tammi, K., Smolowitz, R., Lundgren, K.M., Post, A.F. and Gomez-Chiarri, M. (2019). Bacterial Community Dynamics in an Oyster Hatchery in Response to Probiotic Treatment. Frontiers in Microbiology 10, 1060. doi:10.3389/FMICB.2019.01060&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This work was supported by NSF Graduate Research Fellowship 1244657 to RJS, USDA AFRI 2016-67016-24905 and USDA NRAC 2258-Z55106 to DCR, DRN, and MG-C. This material is based upon work conducted at a Rhode Island NSF EPSCoR research facility, the Genomics and Sequencing Center, supported in part by the National Science Foundation EPSCoR Cooperative Agreements 0554548, EPS-1004057, and OIA-1655221.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
